Skip to main content
🦜🔗 LangChain 0.0.107

Getting Started

Quickstart Guide
Modules

Prompt Templates
LLMs
Document Loaders
Utils
Indexes
Chains
Agents
Memory
Chat
Use Cases

Agents
Chatbots
Generate Examples
Data Augmented Generation
Question Answering
Summarization
Evaluation
Model Comparison
Reference

Installation
Integrations
API References
Ecosystem

LangChain Ecosystem
Additional Resources

LangChainHub
Glossary
LangChain Gallery
Deployments
Tracing
Discord
Production Support
Quickstart Guide
This tutorial gives you a quick walkthrough about building an end-to-end language model application with LangChain.

Installation
To get started, install LangChain with the following command:

pip install langchain
Environment Setup
Using LangChain will usually require integrations with one or more model providers, data stores, apis, etc.

For this example, we will be using OpenAI’s APIs, so we will first need to install their SDK:

pip install openai
We will then need to set the environment variable in the terminal.

export OPENAI_API_KEY="..."
Alternatively, you could do this from inside the Jupyter notebook (or Python script):

import os
os.environ["OPENAI_API_KEY"] = "..."
Building a Language Model Application
Now that we have installed LangChain and set up our environment, we can start building our language model application.

LangChain provides many modules that can be used to build language model applications. Modules can be combined to create more complex applications, or be used individually for simple applications.

previous

Welcome to LangChain

next

Prompt Templates

Contents
Installation
Environment Setup
Building a Language Model Application
By Harrison Chase

© Copyright 2022, Harrison Chase.

Read the Docs
 latest